伙计们  有个坏消息  什么
Hey, you guys. I got some bad news.  What?
这样怎么卖得出去报纸
That's no way to sell newspapers.
试试"号外  号外  快来买啊"
Try, "Extra! Extra! Read all about it!"
不  莫妮卡的餐厅在纽约邮报上的评价很差
No. Monica's restaurant got a horrible review in the Post.
我不希望她看到
I didn't want her to see it,
所以跑遍附近报摊买下了所有报纸
so I ran around and bought all the copies I could find.
确实很糟糕  我一直都被批得很凶
This is bad. And I've had my bad share of bad reviews.
我还记得我第一次被赞美
I still remember my first good one, though:
《我们的小镇》的其他所有方面
"Everything else in this production of Our Town
都很差劲
was simply terrible.
乔伊·崔比安尼无可救药
Joey Tribbiani was abysmal."
我的天啊  看看这些报纸
Oh, my God! Look at all the newspapers.
评价一定很不错  对吧
It must be a good review. Is it great?
我的天啊
Oh, dear God.
但好消息是方圆两条街内
But the good news is, no one in a twoblock radius
没有人会知道
will ever know.
曼哈顿其他的人呢   他们都会知道
What about the rest of Manattan?  They all know.
天啊  这太可怕了  我觉得好丢脸
Oh, my God, this is horrible. I'm so humiliated.
人家不是说嘛
Yeah, but you know what they say, Mon,
没有所谓的负面报导
there's no such thing as bad press.
你不觉得"主厨做的鬼头刀难吃极了"
You don't think that umm, "The chef's Mahi Mahi was awful awful,"
是负面报导吗
is bad press?
那又不是我写的
I didn't write it.
天啊  他说得对吗  我很逊吗   不
God, is he right? Am I awful?  Oh, no!
莫妮卡  听我说
Monica, you listen to me, okay?
我这么说不是因为我是你朋友
I'm not just saying this because I'm your friend.
而是因为这是事实
I'm saying it 'cause it's the truth.
你的菜品无可救药
Your food is abysmal!
《老友记》  第八季  第21集  烹饪班
Friends S08E21 The One With The Cooking Class
罗斯  怎么了
Ross?  What? What?
我好心慌啊  是吗
I am freaking out!  Are you?
我的预产期就在一星期后
My due date is in one week!
你为什么不睡觉   只剩七天
What are you doing up?  That is seven days.
我睡前喝了太多水
Okay, look. I had a lot of water before I went to bed.
我们能不能等会...  不  罗斯
Can we do this after...?  No, no, no, no, Ross!
所有大件用品我们都还没买
Please, come on we do not have any of the big stuff we need!
我们没买尿布桌  也没买摇篮
We do not a changing table! We do not have a crib!
我们甚至没有尿布清洁回收服务
We do not have a diaper service.
你现在提起尿布可真搞笑
Funny you should mention diapers.
我是认真的  没什么好担心的
I'm serious.  There's nothing to worry about.
我们还有大把时间
We have plenty of time.
西十街有家很棒的婴儿用品专卖店
There's a great baby furniture store on west 10th.
我们明天就过去
Tomorrow, we will go there
买齐所有要用的东西  好吗
and we will get you everything that you need. Okay?
好吧  谢谢你  太棒了  谢谢
Okay. Thank you. That's great. Thank you.
等等  西十街在哪里
Wait! Where on west 10th? Because there's this
因为那里有家不错的鞋店...
really cute shoe store that has like this little...
好吧  你要是想做这个
Okay. If you're gonna do this,
那我就去做那个了
then I'm gonna go do that, so...
等一下  罗斯  抱歉  还有一件事
Wait, Ross! I'm sorry, one more thing.
好
Yeah.
我们的情况  我们对彼此的意义
Our situation, you know, what we mean to each other...
我们要一起抚养孩子
...and, I mean, we're having this baby together
我们住在一起...
and we live together...
这难道不是很奇怪吗
Isn't that...? Isn't that weird?
我只是在开玩笑  你可以去上厕所了
I'm just kidding. You can go pee.
莫妮卡  我记不清了
Hey, Monica, I can't remember.
我们约好在这里还是电影院里碰面
Did we say we were gonna meet here or at the movie?
我们约好在电影院见  但...
We said at the movies, but...
我们电影院见
Okay, I'll see you there.
乔伊  既然你来了...
Joey, now that you're here...?
碰面之前可以先和你们待会
I'll hang out till I have to meet you.
你为什么不去
How come you're not going?
我去不成  我要准备新工作的面试
I can't. I've got a job interview I have to get ready for.
你不是已经有工作了吗
I thought you already have a job.
大家竟然还说你不太关心别人
And they say you don't pay attention.
这份工作比之前好很多
No, this is a much better job.
职位是公司副总栽
It's vice president of the company
这家公司为其他公司
that does data reconfiguration
做数据重构和统计保理
and statistical factoring for other companies.
你怎么可能懂这些东西
Wow. How do you know how to do that?
那就是我现在的工作
That's what I do now.
乔伊  来尝尝  什么东西
Joey? Come taste this.  What is it?
还记得给我差评的那个人吗
Remember the guy that gave me a bad review? Well...
我要报复他
I'm getting my revenge.
你把他煮了
You cooked him?
不  他在新校开了一堂美食鉴赏课
No. He teaches a course on food criticism at the New School,
所以看电影之前  我要过去找他
so before we go to the movies I wanna go by there
让他再尝尝我的马赛鱼汤
and make him try my bouillabaisse again.
我等不及要看明天的邮报头版了
I can't wait to read the front page of the Post tomorrow:
"餐厅评鉴家承认  我错怪了莫妮卡"
"Restaurant reviewer admits: I was wrong about Monica."
头版
The front page?
你还真是坐井观天啊
You really do live in your own little world, don't you?
需要我们提供送货服务吗
Do you want these things delivered,
盖勒先生  盖勒太太
Mr. And Mrs. Geller?
不  不
Oh, no, no.  No, no.
我们没有结婚  我们的孩子快出生了
We're not married.  We are having a baby together
但我们没有结婚
but we're not involved.
我是说我们曾经交往过...
I mean, we were seeing each other a while ago...
但后来我们成了朋友
...but then we were just friends,
有天晚上我们喝醉了
and then there was one drunken night...
好的  陌生人  我们需要送货服务
Or, yes, stranger, we'd like this delivered, please.
麻烦你填一下住址  好的
Why don't you fill out this address card?  Oh, okay.
我发现你们挑了不少恐龙  对
I notice you picked out a lot of dinosaurs items.  Yeah.
其实这也是我们没结婚的原因之一
Actually, that's one of the reasons why we're not a couple.
那是我挑的  我是古生物学家
I chose those. I'm a paleontologist.
真的吗  那太酷了
Really? That is so cool.
别因为这事兴奋过头了
Don't get too worked up over it.
你可能以为他是博士  但事实上不然
It sounds like he's a doctor, but he's not.
不  我喜欢古生物学
No. I'm fascinated by paleontology.
你看过华特·艾瓦瑞兹的书吗
Have you read the Walter Alvarez book?
那是我的教科书
Yeah. I teach it in my class.
天啊  我站在收银台
Oh, my god. Standing at a cash register,
手里拿着信用卡  快要无聊死了
I'm holding a credit card, and I'm bored.
我喜欢你住的社区
I love your neighborhood.
街角有家很棒的健身房
There's a great gym right around the corner from your building.
我就在那里健身  我看得出来你有健身
That's my gym.  I could tell you work out.
一位喜欢健身的古生物学家
A paleontologist who works out.
你跟印第安纳·琼斯一样
You're like Indiana Jones.
我确实很像印第安纳·琼斯
I am like Indiana Jones.
嗨  菲比  宝宝的东西买得怎么样了
Hi, Pheebs.  Hey! Oh, how did baby shopping go?
太棒了  我们需要的东西都买到了
Great! We got everything we needed.
罗斯差点拿到清单上没有的东西
Oh, and Ross almost got something that wasn't on the list.
一个妓女
A whore.
什么
What?
我们正在付帐
We were paying for our stuff,
有个女销售员开始对他调情
and this sales woman just started flirting with him.
你能相信吗
Can you believe that?
她知道你们没有结婚吗  知道
Did she know you two weren't married?  Yeah.
天啊
Oh, my God.
一个女人泡一个单身男人
Well, the idea... A woman flirting with a single man?
我们得通知教会的长老  不
We must alert the church elders.  No.
你不了解  你没看到她多不要脸
You don't understand. You didn't see how brazen she was.
你好像在吃醋  我才没有
Sounds like you're jealous.  No, I'm not.
我只是觉得那是不对的
I just think it's wrong.
我是说我就快生了...
I mean, here I am, about to pop...
而他却在荡妇专卖店泡女人
...and he's out picking up some shopgirl at SlutsRUs?
真的有那种地方吗
Is that a real place?
他们在招人吗
Are they hiring?
嘿  菲比  肥婆
Hey, Phoebe. Fatty.
你为什么那么高兴
Chandler, why so fancy?
我得到一个面试机会  待遇很不错
Well, I got a job interview. It's kinda a big deal too.
薪水比之前高很多
It's a lot more money
我要做数据重构和统计保理工作
and I'd be doing data reconfiguration and statistical factoring.
我认识一个人就是做那行的
I think I know someone who does that.
那就是我
Me. I do that.
我看起来还好吧  我好紧张
So, seriously, do I look okay? I'm nervous.
对  你看起来棒极了
Oh, yeah. You really look great.
别抱太高希望
You know, just don't get your hopes up.
为什么  你要去面试
Why not?  Well, the interview.
所以呢  你知道的
What about it?  You know.
你给人留的第一印象都不太好
You don't make a very good first impression.
什么  你不知道啊
What?  Oh, you don't know.
你是说真的吗
Are you serious?
我第一次见到你  你是这样的
Yes, when I first met you, you were like:
我就想说...
I was like:
我做了什么让你不爽
What is it that I do?
你太刻意想要讲笑话
It's just, like, you're trying too hard, always making jokes...
你显得太心急了
You just come off a little needy.
我们第一次见面时  你喜欢我吗
Did you like me when we first met?
钱德勒  我不想骗你
Chandler, I'm not gonna lie to you.
但我要离你远点
But I am gonna run away from you.
我是莫妮卡·盖勒  亚利山多洛斯的主厨
Hi. I'm Monica Geller, chef at Allessandro's.
现在还是
Still?
我觉得你给我的评价很不公平
I think the things that you said about me are really unfair,
我想让你再尝尝我做的马赛鱼汤
and I would like for you to give my bouillabaisse another chance.
我实在不明白自己为何要再尝一次
I don't see why I'd do that to myself again.
不吃就泼你脸上
Either eat it or be in it.
汤匙
Spoon?
你觉得如何  我很为难...
So what do you think?  I'm torn...
不知该实话实说  还是避免挨揍
...between my integrity and my desire to avoid a beating.
但我得老实说
But I must be honest.
你的汤无药可救
Your soup is abysmal.
干得漂亮
Thatta girl!
我们该走了  新的一班要上课了
We should get out of here, there's a new class coming in.
欢迎大家参加烹调入门班
Welcome to Introduction to Cooking.
在开始上课之前
Now, before we start,
谁能告诉我荷兰酱
Can anyone tell me the difference between
跟蛋黄酱的差别
hollandaise and bearnaise sauce?
我知道  请说
I can.  Okay, go ahead.
两者都放了蛋黄跟奶油
Well, they both have a egg yolk and butter base.
但蛋黄酱有放葱
But a bearnaise has shallots,
雪维菜  最重要的是还有龙嵩
chervil, and most importantly, tarragon.
非常好  你叫什么名字
Very good. What's your name?
莫妮卡
Monica.
莫妮卡  你来当班长吧  好啊
Monica, You go to the head of the class!  Okay!
这些玩意占了好多空间
This stuff takes up a lot of room.
你说要一直照顾本  这话是认真的吗
How serious are you about keeping Ben in your life?
我儿子吗  我非常认真
My son? Pretty serious.
嗨  凯蒂  你来这里做什么
Hi, Katie. What are you doing here?
送货员出发之后  我才发现他们忘了这个
The delivery went out to you and I realize they forgot this.
它一定很显眼
It must have been obvious,
因为这是你店里唯一剩下的东西
since it was the only thing left in your store.
听着  老实说
Listen, to be honest,
我的工作不包括送货到家服务
home deliveries aren't really part of my job description.
我是来这里约你的
Oh, I actually came here to ask you out.
听起来很棒
Oh. Wow. Yeah, that sounds great.
我现在就把这个放回口袋
I'm just gonna put this back in my pocket
假装什么都没发生过
and pretend that didn't happen.
我现在就有空  你想喝杯咖啡吗
Yeah, actually I'm free now. You want to get coffee..?
没问题  饥渴的贱人
Sure.  Horny bitch.
不  你才是个饥渴的贱人
No, you're a horny bitch!
祝你们玩得愉快
You guys go and have a good time.
我去拿我的外套跟鞭子
I'm just gonna grab my coat. And my whip.
因为我像印第安纳·琼斯
You know, because of Indiana Jones.
不是因为我喜欢性虐待
Not because I'm into S & M.
我没有怪癖  你知道吗
I'm not into anything weird, you know?
我只喜欢一般的性爱
Just normal sex.
我去拿外套
So I'm gonna grab my coat.
你今天过得很不错嘛
So you had a good day, huh?
赚了一大笔佣金  泡上了准爸爸
Big commission, picked up a daddy.
你对这事没意见吧
Are you okay with this?
当然  拜托  你们好好玩吧
Oh, yeah. Yeah, please. You guys have fun.
好吧  好
Okay.  Yeah.
很高兴能见到你
Nice to see you.
我也是  你看起来漂亮极了
Oh, and it was great to see you too. And you look fantastic.
不过你有颗扣子忘了扣  事实上我...
Although you missed a button.  Oh, actually, I...
好吧  我知道你的意图了
Oh, okay, I see what you're doing there.
我不敢相信  我的形象有那么糟
I can't even believe this. I really come off that badly?
那没什么  相处久了你会稳重下来
It's okay. You calm down after a while...
大家就会了解到你有多体贴  多靠谱
...and then people see how wonderful you really are.
好吧  我相信这次面试会维持好几个星期
Good. Because I'm sure this interview will last weeks.
好吧  别惊慌  我会帮你的
All right, don't freak out, okay? I will help you.
你什么时候出发  一小时后
How long before you have to leave?  An hour.
我帮不了你  菲比...
I can't help you.  Phoebe...
我们尽力而为吧
Alright, we'll do our best, okay?
假如我是面试官
So let's say that I'm the interviewer
我第一次跟你见面
and I'm meeting you for the first time.
好吧  请进  我是瑞吉娜·费兰吉
Okay.  Hi. Come on in. I'm Regina Phalanges.
钱德勒·宾  宾
Chandler Bing.  Oh, Bing.
你的名字很罕见
What an unusual name.
你应该见见我的巴达叔叔
You should meet my Uncle Bada.
我自己出去吧
I'll let myself out.
你的意大利宽条面有点干
Your Fettuccini Alfredo looks a little dry,
你放奶酪了吗
did you use all your cheese?
你说"放"
When you say "use,"
是指"当烹饪前点心吃掉"吗
do you mean "eat as a precooking snack"?
那奶油呢  吃了奶酪  我口很渴
And the cream?  Cheese makes me thirsty.
好吧  我们继续  好吧
Okay. Let's move on.  All right.
莫妮卡做的菜味道很香
Something smells good over at Monica's station.
天啊  这简直太好吃了
My God! This is absolutely amazing!
你以前从来没做过这道菜吗
You've never made this before?
没有  我对烹饪一窍不通
Oh, no. I don't know anything about cooking.
我都不知道水冒泡之后是怎么回事
I had to ask what it was called when the water makes those bubbles.
向主厨致意
Hats off to the chef.
你嘴里全是吃的  我没听清你说什么
I'm sorry. Your mouth was full. I didn't hear what you said.
跟谁致意  主厨
Hats off to who now?  The chef!
没错
That's right!
如有幸被录用  你会发现我不会事必躬亲
I think you'll find if I come to work here, I don't micromanage.
我不害怕把事情交给下属去做
I don't shy away from delegating.
很高兴知道这点
That's good to know.
我们不要只谈那些你不会去做的事...
But let's stop focusing on what you don't do...
我们来谈谈你会去做的事
...and focus on what you do do.
我会...
What I do do...
为我的下属们营造
is manage to create an atmosphere of support
一种团队互助的氛围
for the people working with me.
了解  你很巧妙地避开了"会做"这个问题
I see. Nice sidestep on the "do do" thing by the way.
刚才是我人生中最漫长的三十秒
Hardest thing I've ever done in my life.
你得出发了
Oh, you gotta go!
别担心  你准备好了  真的吗
Don't worry. You're ready.  Really?
当然  千万不要跟着你的直觉走
Absolutely! Just fight all your natural instincts,
你会表现得很棒
and you'll be great.
莫妮卡  我的明星学生
Monica, my star student.
你之前那么称呼过我
You called me that before,
所以我就擅作主张用铝箔纸做了一颗星星
so I took the liberty and fashioned a star out of aluminium foil.
别觉得压力太大
Now, no pressure.
如果你喜欢我的饼干  就奖我一颗星星
If you like my cookies, you give me the star.
好耶  星星
Wow, a star!
我知道你们都恨我  对不起  但我不在乎
I know you all hate me, and I'm sorry, but I don't care.
好吧  乔伊  下一个是你  是的
Okay, Joey, you're up next.  Yeah.
天啊  这简直太好吃了
Oh, my God! This is amazing!
我给你评"优"
You get an A.
我在学校里得到优  我也算是书呆子了
I got an A? In school? Hey, I'm a dork!
乔伊  我非常以你为荣
Joey, I'm so proud of you.
我想你该把你的星星给他  你说什么
I think you should give him your star.  Excuse me?
他都不知道自己在做什么
He doesn't know what he's doing.
大家都是初学者  没人知道自己在做什么
We're all beginners here. Nobody knows what they're doing.
我知道  我是职业主厨
I do. I'm a professional chef!
少来了  这又不是法律戏剧
Oh, relax. It's not a courtroom drama.
如果你是专业主厨
If you're a professional chef,
为什么要上初级烹调课
why are you taking Introduction to Cooking?
就是嘛
Yeah!
抱歉  我是亚利山多洛斯餐厅的主厨...
I'm sorry. I cook at this restaurant, Allessandro's...
我刚刚得到了差评
...and I just got a really bad review.
亚利山多洛斯
Allessandro's?
我喜欢那个餐馆  是吗
I love that place!  You do?
你是个很棒的主厨  但你的个性有点...
Yes, you're an excellent chef. As a person you're a little...
我是很疯狂  但你喜欢那里的食物
Oh, I'm totally crazy, but you liked the food?
非常喜欢
Very much.
好吧  那我还不赖  我是个好主厨  好吧
Okay, then. I don't stink. I'm a good chef! Okay.
我不想走  我玩得很开心
I don't want to go. I'm having fun.
你们俩付学费了吗
Actually, did either of you pay for this class?
如果我朋友说该走了  我们这就走
Hey, if my friend says it's time to go, it's time to go!
另外  我还负责公司里KL5系统
Also, I was the point person on my company's transition
转换到GR6系统的工作
from the KL5 to GR6 systems.
你一定忙得不可开交
You must have had your hands full.
没错  没错
That I did. That I did.
我们来谈谈你的职责吧
So let's talk a little bit about your duties.
我的职责
My duties?
好吧
All right.
你将负责一整个部门
You'll be heading a whole division,
所以你要担负起很多职责
so you'll have a lot of duties.
我了解  你手下会有30个人
I see.  But there'll be 30 people under you...
你可以把很多工作分配给他们
...so you can dump a certain amount on them.
那太好了  我们可以进一步详谈
Good to know.  We could go into detail...
不用了  我求你
No, don't, I beg of you.
好吧  我们会在星期一回复你
All right. We'll have a definite answer for you on Monday.
但我相信你能很好地融入公司环境
But I can say with some confidence, you'll fit in well here.
真的吗  当然
Really?  Absolutely.
放轻松  你表现得很好
You can relax. You did great.
谢谢  我刚才真的很紧张
Yeah, I gotta say thank you, I was really nervous.
大家都说我太喜欢讲笑话缓和气氛
I'm told I come on too strongly, too many jokes.
要避开"职责"的问题真的很难
And then it was really hard to sidestep that "duty" thing.
责任
Duties?
大粪
Doodies?
便便
Poo?
天啊  这不算数  好吗
Oh, my God. This doesn't count. Okay?
面试已经结束了
The interview was over.
刚刚才是真正的钱德勒·宾
That was the real Chandler Bing in there.
这只是个站在走廊里的疯子
This is just some crazy guy out in the hall.
叫警卫来  走廊上有个疯子
Call security! There's a crazy guy out in the hall!
便便
Poo?
我期待你的来电
I'll look forward to your call.
你约会回来了  你还好吗
You're back from your date.  How are you?
我很好  但那不重要
I'm fine. But that's not important.
重要的是她还好吗
What's important is how was she?
玩得很高兴  我们一起去喝了咖啡
It was fun. We just had coffee.
喝咖啡  在桌子底下有动手动脚吧
Oh, uhhuh, uhhuh, coffee, a little rubrubrub under the table?
怎么了  你不喜欢凯蒂吗
What's going on? Do you not like Katie?
不  她很好
No. No, she was nice.
就是有点淫荡  但谁不是呢
I mean, she was a little slutty, but who isn't?
我喜欢她
Well, I liked her.
你当然喜欢她
Of course you did, Ross.
哪怕是只猩猩叫你印第安纳·琼斯
You'd date a gorilla if it called you
你也会跟她约会
Indiana Jones.
你的孕激素今天又分泌过剩了吗
Did you get a fresh batch of pregnancy hormones today?
没有  只是...凯蒂让我觉得心烦
No. It's just that... Katie bothered me.
为什么  她有哪里不好
Why? What was wrong with her?
她没有哪里不好
There was nothing wrong with her, all right?
她非常可爱
She was perfectly lovely.
好吧  那到底怎么了
Okay. So, what's the matter?
我不希望你跟她约会
I don't want you to date her.
为什么  你在吃醋吗
Why? What, are you jealous?
对  但不是因为我想你跟我交住
Yes. And not because I want you to go out with me.
而是因为我不希望你跟任何人交住
Because I don't want you to go out with anybody.
我知道不该去想这种事情
I know it's a terrible thing to even think this
我也知道这样很不合适
and it's completely inappropriate...
但我希望你全天24小时都能随时
but I want you to be at my constant beck and call,
听从我的差遣
24 hours a day.
我非常抱歉  但这就是我的真实感觉
I'm very sorry, but that is just the way that I feel.
好吧  什么
Okay.  What?
我不约会  我会
I won't date. I'll...
我会一直陪着你
I'll be here with you all the time.
真的吗
Really?
但我的要求很无理
But I'm being so unreasonable.
没错  但你有资格无理取闹
True, but you're allowed to be unreasonable.
你怀了我们的宝宝
You're having our baby.
罗斯  谢谢你
Oh, Ross, thank you. Thank you.
你感觉好点了吗
You feel better?
没有  你把宝宝压在我的膀胱上
No, not really. You're pressing the baby into my bladder...
我得去尿尿
...and now I have to pee.
好吧  瑞秋
Okay.  Rach?
什么事  只有一件事
Yeah?  Just one thing...
我们住在一起  你怀了我们的孩子
We live together. You're having our baby.
我会不跟任何人约会
I'm not gonna see anybody else.
你确定你不想更进一步吗
Are you sure you don't want something more?
我不知道  或许吧
Wow. I don't know, maybe...
瑞秋  我只是在开你玩笑
Oh, Rach, I was just messing around.
就像昨晚我要尿尿你逗我那样
Like you did last night when I had to pee?
我就知道
Oh! I knew that.
我就知道  我也是在开你玩笑
I knew that! I was just messing with you too!
好吧  因为你看起来似乎...
Okay. Because for a minute you seemed...
不  那是...  但你像是真的...
No, it's just... ...like you actually...
那只是因为我很会开玩笑
That's just because I'm such a good messer!
瑞秋  什么
Rach?  Yeah?
你不上厕所吗  对
The bathroom?  Right.
我非常开心  我学会了烤饼干  还吃了美食
I had a great time. I learned how to bake, ate great food.
这是我从七年级后第一次得到优等
It's my first A since 7th grade and...
我这次甚至都没有跟老师上床
I didn't even sleep with the teacher this time.
你看  初级表演班  对
Oh, look. Acting for Beginners.  Yeah.
你想找点优越感吗  来吧
Wanna feel good about yourself?  What the hell!
我们从基础开始吧
All right. Let's start with some basics.
谁能告诉我后台
Can anybody tell me what the difference
跟前台的差别
between upstage and downstage is?
我们就不该进来
Yeah, this was a stupid idea.